<?xml version="1.0"?>
<registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
  <registryObject group="Australian Synchrotron">
    <key>{{key}}</key>
    <originatingSource>{{originating_source}}</originatingSource>
    <collection type="dataset">
      <name type="primary">
        <namePart>{{experiment_name}}</namePart>

      </name>
      <location>
        <address>
          <electronic type="email">
            <value>SAXSWAXS@synchrotron.org.au</value>
          </electronic>
        </address>
      </location>

      <coverage>
        <temporal>
          <date type="dateFrom" dateFormat="UTC">{{experiment_end_date}}</date>
        </temporal>
      </coverage>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>synchrotron.org.au/Staff/NigelKirby</key>
        <relation type="isOwnedBy"/>

      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>synchrotron.org.au/Staff/NigelKirby</key>
        <relation type="hasCollector"/>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>synchrotron.org.au/Staff/AdrianHawley</key>
        <relation type="hasCollector"/>

      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>synchrotron.org.au/Staff/StephenMudie</key>
        <relation type="hasCollector"/>
      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>synchrotron.org.au/Staff/NigelKirby</key>
        <relation type="isManagedBy"/>

      </relatedObject>
      <relatedObject>
        <key>synchrotron.org.au/SAXSWAXS</key>
        <relation type="isProducedBy"/>
      </relatedObject>
      <subject type="anzsrc-for">029904</subject>
      <subject type="local">NIST CRM 660a</subject>

      <subject type="local">LaB6 (Lanthanum Hexaboride)</subject>
      <subject type="local">calibration</subject>
      <description type="full">Calibration data for SAXS and WAXS (Small and Wide Angle X-Ray Scattering) from the Australian Synchrotron. SAXS calibrated in the normal way using silver behenate. WAXS was calibrated using an attenuated direct beam shot of NIST Certified Reference Material 660a (LaB6) taken in normal incidence. The accuracy of the WAXS calibration can be seen in data then taken at the rotated WAXS detector position.

This dataset contains a complete SAXS/WAXS instrument calibration. All SAXS and WAXS experiments rely on empirical calibration of angle space from known materials, such as certified materials. Calibrations are done for every experiment on the beamline, typically during beamline setup. Each calibration is applied to the data taken on that setup.

This data set is also useful for describing the accuracy of WAXS data taken on the beamline after careful calibration, since the LaB6 used is a NIST Certified Reference Material with d-spacing’s measured to high accuracy.</description>
      <description type="note">Configuration:

SAXS/WAXS setup. Assymmetric nose cone. 7.2 m nominal SAXS camera length, short WAXS camera length. 10.000 keV incident beam (calibrated using Zn-foil edge scan to within ±2 eV).

Sample Preparation:

SAXS: silver behenate, mounted in flat plate geometry at sample position.

WAXS NIST CRM 660a, mounted in 0.5 mm capillary at sample position, continually oscillated in omega rotation during data collection.</description>
      <description type="note">Information on the format and analysis of the data in this collection is available from the SAXS/WAXS beamline link on this page (Is produced by:).</description>
      <description type="rights">This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Australia License (see the Creative Commons relatedInfo link on this page).</description>

      <relatedInfo>
        <identifier type="uri">http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/au/deed.en</identifier>
        <title>Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Australia License</title>
      </relatedInfo>
      <relatedInfo>
        <identifier type="uri">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lanthanum_hexaboride</identifier>
        <title>Lanthanum hexaboride @ wikipedia</title>

      </relatedInfo>
    </collection>
  </registryObject>
</registryObjects>

